<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<playlist>
  <data>
    <item id="name">default</item>
  </data>
  <songs>
    <song>
      <item id="title">JLS ft DEV- she makes me wanna lyrics</item>
      <item id="actualId">YUJP9Zt5ZaEs</item>
      <item id="id">http://gdata.youtube.com/feeds/api/videos/CT9HQTBpuWY</item>
      <item id="keywords">JLS,Dev,She,makes,me,wanna,lyrics,leahmcbeathx</item>
      <item id="content">JLS feat Dev sing 'She makes me wanna' with lyrics lyrics from-lyricsbod.blogspot.com song-itunes.com</item>
    </song>
    <song>
      <item id="title">The Wanted - Glad you came lyrics</item>
      <item id="actualId">YUJP9Zt5ZaE</item>
      <item id="id">http://gdata.youtube.com/feeds/api/videos/YUJP9Zt5ZaE</item>
      <item id="keywords">The,Wanted,Glad,you,came,lyrics,new,song,Rachel4603,full,new single,on,screen,album,full song</item>
      <item id="content">NEW SINGLE! Full song! The Wanted - Glad you came lyrics! :) Released July 10th ! ENJOY!</item>
    </song>
    <song>
      <item id="title">DJ Khaled Feat. Chris Brown, Keyshia Cole &amp; Ne-Yo - Legendary (We The Best Forever 2011)</item>
      <item id="actualId">6XplJtI5xFM</item>
      <item id="id">http://gdata.youtube.com/feeds/api/videos/6XplJtI5xFM</item>
      <item id="keywords">dj khaled,chris brown,keyshia cole,ne-yo,legenday,dj khaled legendary,chris brown legendary,keyshia cole legendary,ne-yo legendary,legendary dj khaled,'legendary,chris,brown,legendary keyshia cole,legendary ne-yo,we the best forever,young money,cash money,ymcmb,new,hip hop,rap,rnb,2011,weareyoungmoneyenttm</item>
      <item id="content">We The Best Forever in stores July 19! DJ Khaled Feat. Chris Brown, Keyshia Cole &amp; Ne-Yo - Legendary (We The Best Forever 2011) DJ Khaled - Legendary DJ Khaled - Legendary DJ Khaled - Legendary DJ Khaled - Legendary DJ Khaled - Legendary</item>
    </song>
    <song>
      <item id="title">SEAN PAUL FT ALEXIS JORDAN - GOT 2 LUV U [HQ SOUND]</item>
      <item id="actualId">y4Vyq_z3VVI</item>
      <item id="id">http://gdata.youtube.com/feeds/api/videos/y4Vyq_z3VVI</item>
      <item id="keywords">Sean,Paul,Alexis,Jordan,Got,Luv,to,love,you,lyrics,song,full,album,new,screen,Laksida,want,girl</item>
      <item id="content">www.youtube.com official song Ryan Tedder Not to love you i do not own the rights of the song ) its not mine AMAZING SONG www.youtube.com NEW 2011 Hot Song www.youtube.com Sean Paul's new single "Got 2 Luv U" Ft. Alexis Jordan Got to love you! With LYRICS Got to love you! Got to love you! Got to love you! Girl don't steal... report you don't ... off the ground... pick a... only... self alone ... baby telling me own... alone make you start... like a star. Alexis Jordan -- Chorus: I, I'll do anything I could for ya Boy you're my only I, I'm gonna flip these beats on ya You don't even know me Cause I am, I... I don't even want to fight, fight, fight Said I am, I... I ain't even gonna fight it 2 x Got to love you! Got to love you! Got to love you! Got to love you! Girl I'll be alone... insecurity I'ma start remind you... set you free some... That's why me... girl not ready for... check in... Make you lose... Chorus: I, I'll do anything I could for ya Boy you're my only I, I'm gonna flip these beats on ya You don't even know me Cause I am, I... I don't even want to fight, fight, fight Said I am, I... I ain't even gonna fight it 2 x Got to love you! Got to love you! Got to love you! Got to love you! It was fine... in your own... But know it around Boy you got me, you can't ignore it got 2 luv u sean paul alexis jordan sean paul got 2 luv u 2 got 2 luv u sean paul ft alexis jordan got to love ya sean paul alexis jordan sean paul got to love you got to love ya sean paul sean paul</item>
    </song>
    <song>
      <item id="title">Nayer feat. Pitbull &amp; Mohombi - Suavemente (Prod. by RedOne) 2011</item>
      <item id="actualId">r9JxA3jigmw</item>
      <item id="id">http://gdata.youtube.com/feeds/api/videos/r9JxA3jigmw</item>
      <item id="keywords">Nayer 2011,Nayer,Nayer Suavemente,Suavemente Pitbull,Pitbull 2011,Pitbull Nayer,Nayer Mohombi,Mohombi 2011,Mohombi Suavemente,Nayer feat. Pitbull &amp; Mohombi,Nayer ft. Pitbull &amp; Mohombi</item>
      <item id="content">FACEBOOK: www.facebook.com Nayer ft. Pitbull &amp; Mohombi - Suavemente (Prod. by RedOne) Nayer feat. Pitbull - Suavemente (Prod. by RedOne) Nayer feat. - Suavemente (Prod. by RedOne) Pitbull feat. Nayer - Suavemente _____________________________ Add Me On Facebook Please (; www.facebook.com Nayer - Suavemente Nayer - Suavemente Nayer - Suavemente</item>
    </song>
    <song>
      <item id="title">Pitbull - Rain Over Me ft. Marc Anthony (Official Music Video)(Lyrics)</item>
      <item id="actualId">jQqoujabDP4</item>
      <item id="id">http://gdata.youtube.com/feeds/api/videos/jQqoujabDP4</item>
      <item id="keywords">official,anthony,rain,jim,wolf,red,mark,bull,wolves,pit,day,rainy,carpet,director,red bull,blue,casey,riding,dog,nose,cross,terrier,red carpet,rodeo,rocks,light,pit bull,race,staffordshire,bulls,little,mechanical,air,bull terrier,red light</item>
      <item id="content">www.youtube.com [Marc Anthony] Girl my body don't lie I'm outta my mind Let it rain over me I'm rising so high Out of my mind So let it rain over me Ay ay ay Let it rain over me Ay ay ay Let it rain over me [Pitbull] Always a new million Always a new vodka Forty is the new 30 Baby you're a rockstar Dale veterana, que tu sabe Mas de la cuenta, no te hagas Teach me baby, or better yet, Freak me baby, yes, yes I'm freaky baby, I'mma make sure that your peach feels peachy baby No bullshit rods, I like my women sexy classy sassy Powerful yes, they love to get the middle, nasty ow This ain't a game you'll see, you can put the blame on me Dale munequita ahora ahi, and let it rain over me [Marc Anthony] Girl my body don't lie I'm outta my mind Let it rain over me I'm rising so high Out of my mind So let it rain over me Ay ay ay Let it rain over me Ay ay ay Let it rain over me [Pitbull] Always a new million Always a new vodka Latin is the new majority, ya tu sabe Next step la casa blanca No hay carro, no vamos en balsa Mami you know the drill, they won't know what I got 'til they read the will I ain't try, I ain't trying to keep it real I'm trying to keep wealthy that's for real Pero mira que tu estas buena, y mira que tu estas dura Baby no me hables mas, y tiramelo mami chula No games you'll see, you can put the blame on me Dale munequita ahora ahi, and let it rain over me [Marc Anthony] Girl my body don't lie I'm outta my mind Let it rain over me I'm rising so high Out of my</item>
    </song>
  </songs>
</playlist>
